[{"subjectID":"sqdke1x5nr","prolificID":"6604659d90f32e434cb25d96","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21e2bbd321bb8ef8be4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980498549,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"208","question":"Do you consider yourself more of a “cat person” or a “dog person”? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":7886,"timeElapsed":358165},{"subjectID":"sqdke1x5nr","prolificID":"6604659d90f32e434cb25d96","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21e2bbd321bb8ef8be4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980501642,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"208","question":"Do you consider yourself more of a “cat person” or a “dog person”? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":3092,"timeElapsed":361258},{"subjectID":"sqdke1x5nr","prolificID":"6604659d90f32e434cb25d96","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21e2bbd321bb8ef8be4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980508579,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"208","question":"Do you consider yourself more of a “cat person” or a “dog person”? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":6935,"timeElapsed":368195},{"subjectID":"sqdke1x5nr","prolificID":"6604659d90f32e434cb25d96","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21e2bbd321bb8ef8be4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980520078,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"208","question":"Do you consider yourself more of a “cat person” or a “dog person”? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":11498,"timeElapsed":379694},{"subjectID":"sqdke1x5nr","prolificID":"6604659d90f32e434cb25d96","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21e2bbd321bb8ef8be4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980527810,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"208","question":"Do you consider yourself more of a “cat person” or a “dog person”? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":7730,"timeElapsed":387426},{"subjectID":"sqdke1x5nr","prolificID":"6604659d90f32e434cb25d96","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21e2bbd321bb8ef8be4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980536319,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"208","question":"Do you consider yourself more of a “cat person” or a “dog person”? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":8509,"timeElapsed":395935},{"subjectID":"sqdke1x5nr","prolificID":"6604659d90f32e434cb25d96","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21e2bbd321bb8ef8be4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980541674,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"208","question":"Do you consider yourself more of a “cat person” or a “dog person”? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":5353,"timeElapsed":401290},{"subjectID":"sqdke1x5nr","prolificID":"6604659d90f32e434cb25d96","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21e2bbd321bb8ef8be4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980546903,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"208","question":"Do you consider yourself more of a “cat person” or a “dog person”? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":5228,"timeElapsed":406519},{"subjectID":"sqdke1x5nr","prolificID":"6604659d90f32e434cb25d96","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21e2bbd321bb8ef8be4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980550668,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"208","question":"Do you consider yourself more of a “cat person” or a “dog person”? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":3763,"timeElapsed":410283},{"subjectID":"sqdke1x5nr","prolificID":"6604659d90f32e434cb25d96","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21e2bbd321bb8ef8be4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980563273,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"50","question":"What does it mean to “know” somebody or feel close to them?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":11102,"timeElapsed":422889},{"subjectID":"sqdke1x5nr","prolificID":"6604659d90f32e434cb25d96","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21e2bbd321bb8ef8be4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980567671,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"50","question":"What does it mean to “know” somebody or feel close to them?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":4397,"timeElapsed":427287},{"subjectID":"sqdke1x5nr","prolificID":"6604659d90f32e434cb25d96","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21e2bbd321bb8ef8be4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980570543,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"50","question":"What does it mean to “know” somebody or feel close to them?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":2871,"timeElapsed":430159},{"subjectID":"sqdke1x5nr","prolificID":"6604659d90f32e434cb25d96","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21e2bbd321bb8ef8be4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980583868,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"50","question":"What does it mean to “know” somebody or feel close to them?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":13324,"timeElapsed":443484},{"subjectID":"sqdke1x5nr","prolificID":"6604659d90f32e434cb25d96","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21e2bbd321bb8ef8be4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980585618,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What does it mean to “know” somebody or feel close to them?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":51,"rt":1749,"timeElapsed":445234},{"subjectID":"sqdke1x5nr","prolificID":"6604659d90f32e434cb25d96","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21e2bbd321bb8ef8be4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980591080,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"50","question":"What does it mean to “know” somebody or feel close to them?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":5461,"timeElapsed":450696},{"subjectID":"sqdke1x5nr","prolificID":"6604659d90f32e434cb25d96","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21e2bbd321bb8ef8be4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980593829,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"50","question":"What does it mean to “know” somebody or feel close to them?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":2748,"timeElapsed":453445},{"subjectID":"sqdke1x5nr","prolificID":"6604659d90f32e434cb25d96","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21e2bbd321bb8ef8be4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980595476,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"50","question":"What does it mean to “know” somebody or feel close to them?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":1645,"timeElapsed":455092},{"subjectID":"sqdke1x5nr","prolificID":"6604659d90f32e434cb25d96","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21e2bbd321bb8ef8be4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980597414,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"50","question":"What does it mean to “know” somebody or feel close to them?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":1937,"timeElapsed":457030},{"subjectID":"sqdke1x5nr","prolificID":"6604659d90f32e434cb25d96","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21e2bbd321bb8ef8be4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980598993,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"50","question":"What does it mean to “know” somebody or feel close to them?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":1577,"timeElapsed":458609},{"subjectID":"sqdke1x5nr","prolificID":"6604659d90f32e434cb25d96","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21e2bbd321bb8ef8be4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980605385,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"191","question":"Do you routinely watch sports? Do you have a favorite sport or team? If you had to choose a new team or sport to follow, what would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":52,"rt":5255,"timeElapsed":465001},{"subjectID":"sqdke1x5nr","prolificID":"6604659d90f32e434cb25d96","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21e2bbd321bb8ef8be4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980607323,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"191","question":"Do you routinely watch sports? Do you have a favorite sport or team? If you had to choose a new team or sport to follow, what would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":52,"rt":1936,"timeElapsed":466939},{"subjectID":"sqdke1x5nr","prolificID":"6604659d90f32e434cb25d96","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21e2bbd321bb8ef8be4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980609393,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"191","question":"Do you routinely watch sports? Do you have a favorite sport or team? If you had to choose a new team or sport to follow, what would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":2069,"timeElapsed":469009},{"subjectID":"sqdke1x5nr","prolificID":"6604659d90f32e434cb25d96","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21e2bbd321bb8ef8be4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980613332,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"191","question":"Do you routinely watch sports? Do you have a favorite sport or team? If you had to choose a new team or sport to follow, what would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":3937,"timeElapsed":472948},{"subjectID":"sqdke1x5nr","prolificID":"6604659d90f32e434cb25d96","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21e2bbd321bb8ef8be4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980615403,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"191","question":"Do you routinely watch sports? Do you have a favorite sport or team? If you had to choose a new team or sport to follow, what would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":2070,"timeElapsed":475019},{"subjectID":"sqdke1x5nr","prolificID":"6604659d90f32e434cb25d96","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21e2bbd321bb8ef8be4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980617906,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"191","question":"Do you routinely watch sports? Do you have a favorite sport or team? If you had to choose a new team or sport to follow, what would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":2502,"timeElapsed":477522},{"subjectID":"sqdke1x5nr","prolificID":"6604659d90f32e434cb25d96","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21e2bbd321bb8ef8be4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980620016,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"191","question":"Do you routinely watch sports? Do you have a favorite sport or team? If you had to choose a new team or sport to follow, what would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":2109,"timeElapsed":479632},{"subjectID":"sqdke1x5nr","prolificID":"6604659d90f32e434cb25d96","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21e2bbd321bb8ef8be4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980622271,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"191","question":"Do you routinely watch sports? Do you have a favorite sport or team? If you had to choose a new team or sport to follow, what would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":2254,"timeElapsed":481887},{"subjectID":"sqdke1x5nr","prolificID":"6604659d90f32e434cb25d96","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21e2bbd321bb8ef8be4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980625175,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"191","question":"Do you routinely watch sports? Do you have a favorite sport or team? If you had to choose a new team or sport to follow, what would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":2903,"timeElapsed":484791},{"subjectID":"sqdke1x5nr","prolificID":"6604659d90f32e434cb25d96","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21e2bbd321bb8ef8be4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980629357,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"75","question":"If you opened a restaurant, what would it be like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":2954,"timeElapsed":488973},{"subjectID":"sqdke1x5nr","prolificID":"6604659d90f32e434cb25d96","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21e2bbd321bb8ef8be4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980631060,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"75","question":"If you opened a restaurant, what would it be like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":1702,"timeElapsed":490676},{"subjectID":"sqdke1x5nr","prolificID":"6604659d90f32e434cb25d96","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21e2bbd321bb8ef8be4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980632771,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"75","question":"If you opened a restaurant, what would it be like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":51,"rt":1710,"timeElapsed":492387},{"subjectID":"sqdke1x5nr","prolificID":"6604659d90f32e434cb25d96","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21e2bbd321bb8ef8be4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980634996,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"75","question":"If you opened a restaurant, what would it be like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":2224,"timeElapsed":494611},{"subjectID":"sqdke1x5nr","prolificID":"6604659d90f32e434cb25d96","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21e2bbd321bb8ef8be4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980636909,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"75","question":"If you opened a restaurant, what would it be like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":1913,"timeElapsed":496525},{"subjectID":"sqdke1x5nr","prolificID":"6604659d90f32e434cb25d96","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21e2bbd321bb8ef8be4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980639030,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"75","question":"If you opened a restaurant, what would it be like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":2119,"timeElapsed":498646},{"subjectID":"sqdke1x5nr","prolificID":"6604659d90f32e434cb25d96","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21e2bbd321bb8ef8be4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980640543,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"75","question":"If you opened a restaurant, what would it be like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":51,"rt":1512,"timeElapsed":500159},{"subjectID":"sqdke1x5nr","prolificID":"6604659d90f32e434cb25d96","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21e2bbd321bb8ef8be4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980642159,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"75","question":"If you opened a restaurant, what would it be like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":51,"rt":1614,"timeElapsed":501775},{"subjectID":"sqdke1x5nr","prolificID":"6604659d90f32e434cb25d96","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21e2bbd321bb8ef8be4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980644919,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"75","question":"If you opened a restaurant, what would it be like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":2759,"timeElapsed":504535},{"subjectID":"sqdke1x5nr","prolificID":"6604659d90f32e434cb25d96","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21e2bbd321bb8ef8be4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980652710,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"43","question":"What is your least favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":6562,"timeElapsed":512325},{"subjectID":"sqdke1x5nr","prolificID":"6604659d90f32e434cb25d96","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21e2bbd321bb8ef8be4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980654469,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"43","question":"What is your least favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":51,"rt":1758,"timeElapsed":514084},{"subjectID":"sqdke1x5nr","prolificID":"6604659d90f32e434cb25d96","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21e2bbd321bb8ef8be4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980655989,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"43","question":"What is your least favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":1519,"timeElapsed":515605},{"subjectID":"sqdke1x5nr","prolificID":"6604659d90f32e434cb25d96","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21e2bbd321bb8ef8be4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980660397,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"43","question":"What is your least favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":4407,"timeElapsed":520013},{"subjectID":"sqdke1x5nr","prolificID":"6604659d90f32e434cb25d96","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21e2bbd321bb8ef8be4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980662137,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"43","question":"What is your least favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":1739,"timeElapsed":521753},{"subjectID":"sqdke1x5nr","prolificID":"6604659d90f32e434cb25d96","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21e2bbd321bb8ef8be4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980664369,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"43","question":"What is your least favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":51,"rt":2230,"timeElapsed":523985},{"subjectID":"sqdke1x5nr","prolificID":"6604659d90f32e434cb25d96","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21e2bbd321bb8ef8be4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980666201,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"43","question":"What is your least favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":1832,"timeElapsed":525817},{"subjectID":"sqdke1x5nr","prolificID":"6604659d90f32e434cb25d96","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21e2bbd321bb8ef8be4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980668050,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"43","question":"What is your least favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":1847,"timeElapsed":527666},{"subjectID":"sqdke1x5nr","prolificID":"6604659d90f32e434cb25d96","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21e2bbd321bb8ef8be4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980671346,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"43","question":"What is your least favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":3295,"timeElapsed":530962},{"subjectID":"sqdke1x5nr","prolificID":"6604659d90f32e434cb25d96","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21e2bbd321bb8ef8be4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980679762,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"143","question":"What is your favorite holiday? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":6945,"timeElapsed":539378},{"subjectID":"sqdke1x5nr","prolificID":"6604659d90f32e434cb25d96","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21e2bbd321bb8ef8be4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980681604,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"143","question":"What is your favorite holiday? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":51,"rt":1841,"timeElapsed":541220},{"subjectID":"sqdke1x5nr","prolificID":"6604659d90f32e434cb25d96","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21e2bbd321bb8ef8be4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980684103,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"143","question":"What is your favorite holiday? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":2498,"timeElapsed":543719},{"subjectID":"sqdke1x5nr","prolificID":"6604659d90f32e434cb25d96","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21e2bbd321bb8ef8be4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980687382,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"143","question":"What is your favorite holiday? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":3279,"timeElapsed":546998},{"subjectID":"sqdke1x5nr","prolificID":"6604659d90f32e434cb25d96","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21e2bbd321bb8ef8be4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980689546,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"143","question":"What is your favorite holiday? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":2163,"timeElapsed":549162},{"subjectID":"sqdke1x5nr","prolificID":"6604659d90f32e434cb25d96","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21e2bbd321bb8ef8be4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980693470,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"143","question":"What is your favorite holiday? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":3922,"timeElapsed":553086},{"subjectID":"sqdke1x5nr","prolificID":"6604659d90f32e434cb25d96","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21e2bbd321bb8ef8be4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980695604,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"143","question":"What is your favorite holiday? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":2133,"timeElapsed":555220},{"subjectID":"sqdke1x5nr","prolificID":"6604659d90f32e434cb25d96","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21e2bbd321bb8ef8be4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980697606,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"143","question":"What is your favorite holiday? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":2000,"timeElapsed":557222},{"subjectID":"sqdke1x5nr","prolificID":"6604659d90f32e434cb25d96","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21e2bbd321bb8ef8be4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980699944,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"143","question":"What is your favorite holiday? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":2337,"timeElapsed":559560},{"subjectID":"sqdke1x5nr","prolificID":"6604659d90f32e434cb25d96","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21e2bbd321bb8ef8be4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980709498,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"198","question":"Do you know any “party tricks”? If so, describe them. If not, describe one you would like to learn.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":8320,"timeElapsed":569114},{"subjectID":"sqdke1x5nr","prolificID":"6604659d90f32e434cb25d96","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21e2bbd321bb8ef8be4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980711563,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"198","question":"Do you know any “party tricks”? If so, describe them. If not, describe one you would like to learn.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":2064,"timeElapsed":571179},{"subjectID":"sqdke1x5nr","prolificID":"6604659d90f32e434cb25d96","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21e2bbd321bb8ef8be4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980714848,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"198","question":"Do you know any “party tricks”? If so, describe them. If not, describe one you would like to learn.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":3284,"timeElapsed":574464},{"subjectID":"sqdke1x5nr","prolificID":"6604659d90f32e434cb25d96","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21e2bbd321bb8ef8be4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980717046,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"198","question":"Do you know any “party tricks”? If so, describe them. If not, describe one you would like to learn.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":2197,"timeElapsed":576662},{"subjectID":"sqdke1x5nr","prolificID":"6604659d90f32e434cb25d96","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21e2bbd321bb8ef8be4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980720292,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"198","question":"Do you know any “party tricks”? If so, describe them. If not, describe one you would like to learn.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":3245,"timeElapsed":579908},{"subjectID":"sqdke1x5nr","prolificID":"6604659d90f32e434cb25d96","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21e2bbd321bb8ef8be4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980723466,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"198","question":"Do you know any “party tricks”? If so, describe them. If not, describe one you would like to learn.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":3172,"timeElapsed":583081},{"subjectID":"sqdke1x5nr","prolificID":"6604659d90f32e434cb25d96","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21e2bbd321bb8ef8be4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980726789,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"198","question":"Do you know any “party tricks”? If so, describe them. If not, describe one you would like to learn.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":3323,"timeElapsed":586405},{"subjectID":"sqdke1x5nr","prolificID":"6604659d90f32e434cb25d96","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21e2bbd321bb8ef8be4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980730515,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"198","question":"Do you know any “party tricks”? If so, describe them. If not, describe one you would like to learn.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":51,"rt":3724,"timeElapsed":590131},{"subjectID":"sqdke1x5nr","prolificID":"6604659d90f32e434cb25d96","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21e2bbd321bb8ef8be4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980734902,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"198","question":"Do you know any “party tricks”? If so, describe them. If not, describe one you would like to learn.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":4386,"timeElapsed":594518},{"subjectID":"sqdke1x5nr","prolificID":"6604659d90f32e434cb25d96","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21e2bbd321bb8ef8be4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980740266,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Do you know any “party tricks”? If so, describe them. If not, describe one you would like to learn.","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":5363,"timeElapsed":599882},{"subjectID":"sqdke1x5nr","prolificID":"6604659d90f32e434cb25d96","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21e2bbd321bb8ef8be4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980749503,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"156","question":"What is the best TV show or movie that you have seen in the last month? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":7951,"timeElapsed":609119},{"subjectID":"sqdke1x5nr","prolificID":"6604659d90f32e434cb25d96","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21e2bbd321bb8ef8be4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980751573,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"156","question":"What is the best TV show or movie that you have seen in the last month? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":2068,"timeElapsed":611189},{"subjectID":"sqdke1x5nr","prolificID":"6604659d90f32e434cb25d96","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21e2bbd321bb8ef8be4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980753330,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"156","question":"What is the best TV show or movie that you have seen in the last month? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":1756,"timeElapsed":612946},{"subjectID":"sqdke1x5nr","prolificID":"6604659d90f32e434cb25d96","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21e2bbd321bb8ef8be4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980756118,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"156","question":"What is the best TV show or movie that you have seen in the last month? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":2787,"timeElapsed":615734},{"subjectID":"sqdke1x5nr","prolificID":"6604659d90f32e434cb25d96","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21e2bbd321bb8ef8be4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980758402,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"156","question":"What is the best TV show or movie that you have seen in the last month? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":2283,"timeElapsed":618018},{"subjectID":"sqdke1x5nr","prolificID":"6604659d90f32e434cb25d96","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21e2bbd321bb8ef8be4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980760416,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"156","question":"What is the best TV show or movie that you have seen in the last month? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":2013,"timeElapsed":620032},{"subjectID":"sqdke1x5nr","prolificID":"6604659d90f32e434cb25d96","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21e2bbd321bb8ef8be4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980762299,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"156","question":"What is the best TV show or movie that you have seen in the last month? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":1881,"timeElapsed":621915},{"subjectID":"sqdke1x5nr","prolificID":"6604659d90f32e434cb25d96","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21e2bbd321bb8ef8be4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980764959,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"156","question":"What is the best TV show or movie that you have seen in the last month? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":2659,"timeElapsed":624575},{"subjectID":"sqdke1x5nr","prolificID":"6604659d90f32e434cb25d96","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21e2bbd321bb8ef8be4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980767436,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"156","question":"What is the best TV show or movie that you have seen in the last month? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":51,"rt":2476,"timeElapsed":627051},{"subjectID":"sqdke1x5nr","prolificID":"6604659d90f32e434cb25d96","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21e2bbd321bb8ef8be4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980775254,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"56","question":"Would you want to go to space? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":31,"rt":6580,"timeElapsed":634870},{"subjectID":"sqdke1x5nr","prolificID":"6604659d90f32e434cb25d96","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21e2bbd321bb8ef8be4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980778243,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"56","question":"Would you want to go to space? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":2988,"timeElapsed":637859},{"subjectID":"sqdke1x5nr","prolificID":"6604659d90f32e434cb25d96","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21e2bbd321bb8ef8be4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980781994,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"56","question":"Would you want to go to space? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":3749,"timeElapsed":641610},{"subjectID":"sqdke1x5nr","prolificID":"6604659d90f32e434cb25d96","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21e2bbd321bb8ef8be4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980787684,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"56","question":"Would you want to go to space? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":5689,"timeElapsed":647300},{"subjectID":"sqdke1x5nr","prolificID":"6604659d90f32e434cb25d96","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21e2bbd321bb8ef8be4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980792030,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"56","question":"Would you want to go to space? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":4345,"timeElapsed":651646},{"subjectID":"sqdke1x5nr","prolificID":"6604659d90f32e434cb25d96","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21e2bbd321bb8ef8be4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980800398,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"56","question":"Would you want to go to space? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":8366,"timeElapsed":660014},{"subjectID":"sqdke1x5nr","prolificID":"6604659d90f32e434cb25d96","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21e2bbd321bb8ef8be4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980804492,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"56","question":"Would you want to go to space? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":4092,"timeElapsed":664108},{"subjectID":"sqdke1x5nr","prolificID":"6604659d90f32e434cb25d96","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21e2bbd321bb8ef8be4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980807942,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"56","question":"Would you want to go to space? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":3449,"timeElapsed":667558},{"subjectID":"sqdke1x5nr","prolificID":"6604659d90f32e434cb25d96","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21e2bbd321bb8ef8be4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980812067,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"56","question":"Would you want to go to space? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":4124,"timeElapsed":671683},{"subjectID":"sqdke1x5nr","prolificID":"6604659d90f32e434cb25d96","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21e2bbd321bb8ef8be4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980818872,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"100","question":"If you died today, what would be your biggest regret?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":5411,"timeElapsed":678488},{"subjectID":"sqdke1x5nr","prolificID":"6604659d90f32e434cb25d96","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21e2bbd321bb8ef8be4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980822314,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"100","question":"If you died today, what would be your biggest regret?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":3441,"timeElapsed":681930},{"subjectID":"sqdke1x5nr","prolificID":"6604659d90f32e434cb25d96","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21e2bbd321bb8ef8be4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980825070,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"100","question":"If you died today, what would be your biggest regret?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":2755,"timeElapsed":684686},{"subjectID":"sqdke1x5nr","prolificID":"6604659d90f32e434cb25d96","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21e2bbd321bb8ef8be4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980828052,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"100","question":"If you died today, what would be your biggest regret?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":2980,"timeElapsed":687667},{"subjectID":"sqdke1x5nr","prolificID":"6604659d90f32e434cb25d96","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21e2bbd321bb8ef8be4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980830968,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"100","question":"If you died today, what would be your biggest regret?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":2915,"timeElapsed":690584},{"subjectID":"sqdke1x5nr","prolificID":"6604659d90f32e434cb25d96","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21e2bbd321bb8ef8be4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980836864,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"100","question":"If you died today, what would be your biggest regret?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":5895,"timeElapsed":696480},{"subjectID":"sqdke1x5nr","prolificID":"6604659d90f32e434cb25d96","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21e2bbd321bb8ef8be4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980840670,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"100","question":"If you died today, what would be your biggest regret?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":3804,"timeElapsed":700286},{"subjectID":"sqdke1x5nr","prolificID":"6604659d90f32e434cb25d96","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21e2bbd321bb8ef8be4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980844440,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"100","question":"If you died today, what would be your biggest regret?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":3769,"timeElapsed":704055},{"subjectID":"sqdke1x5nr","prolificID":"6604659d90f32e434cb25d96","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21e2bbd321bb8ef8be4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980848835,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"100","question":"If you died today, what would be your biggest regret?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":4395,"timeElapsed":708451}]